teuxdeux.com 2019-03-12

# TeuxDeux / Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of TeuxDeux LLC ("we" or "us") on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on the TeuxDeux mobile application, http:// www.teuxdeux.com and the related services, features, content or applications in connection therewith (collectively, "TeuxDeux"). In connection with your use of TeuxDeux, we receive information about you from various sources, including: (i) through your TeuxDeux user account (your "Account"); (ii) your use of TeuxDeux generally; and (iii) from third party websites and services. When you use TeuxDeux, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, transmission, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") we gather when you are using or accessing TeuxDeux. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our business partners share with us or that we share with our business partners. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, content sources, services and applications ("Third Party Services") that you elect to access through TeuxDeux, or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

### What Information Is Collected by TeuxDeux?

The information we gather enables us to personalize, improve and continue to operate TeuxDeux. In connection with certain aspects of TeuxDeux, we may request, collect and/or display some of your Personal Information. We collect the following types of information from our users.

#### Sign-In Information:

When you create an Account or login using your Facebook or Twitter accounts, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as your username, password and email address. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by creating an account with TeuxDeux and providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you and therefore may not be anonymous. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services, including without limitation, notifications regarding our services. You may unsubscribe from these messages through a link at the bottom of the email messages sent to you, although we regardless reserve the right to contact you when we believe it is necessary, such as for account recovery purposes.

#### User Content:

TeuxDeux allows you to provide content to TeuxDeux. All content submitted by you to TeuxDeux may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your Account. We may continue to disclose such content to third parties in a manner that does not reveal Personal Information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Information Collected From Third Party Services:

Some features of TeuxDeux may allow you to share your TeuxDeux content through Third Party Services and your content from Third Party Services through TeuxDeux. If you choose to connect TeuxDeux to such Third Party Services, we may collect information related to your use of those Third Party Services, such as authentication tokens that allow us to connect to your Third Party Service accounts. We may otherwise collect information about how you are using TeuxDeux to interact with those connected Third Party Services. Note that Third Party Services may have the ability to restrict the information that is provided to us.

#### IP Address Information and Other Information Collected Automatically:

We automatically receive and record information from the TeuxDeux application or your web browser when you interact with TeuxDeux, including your IP address and cookie information. This information is used to facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with TeuxDeux (e.g., what content you have clicked on). Generally, TeuxDeux automatically collects usage information, such as the number and frequency of users accessing TeuxDeux. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to figure out how often individuals use parts of TeuxDeux so that we can analyze and improve them.

#### Email Communications:

We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. We use this confirmation to improve our customer service.

#### Information Collected Using Cookies:

Cookies are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser or application when you access a website or service. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website or service you visit. We use cookies to enable our servers to recognize your web browser or TeuxDeux application and tell us how and when you visit and use TeuxDeux through the web or through an application.

TeuxDeux cookies also allow us to track when you have accessed content through TeuxDeux. Each access is tracked using a unique identifier assigned to you in one or more cookies stored by your web browser or application and associated with TeuxDeux.

TeuxDeux cookies do not, by themselves, contain Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are. As noted, however, we do use cookies to identify that your web browser or application has accessed content through TeuxDeux and may associate that information with your Account if you have one.

This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer or device. For example, third party websites may set their own cookies.

#### Aggregate Information:

We collect statistical information about how people use TeuxDeux ("Aggregate Information"). Some of this information is derived from Personal Information, such as your location (which, in turn, can be derived from your IP address or through location based services used by your device). This statistical information is not Personal Information and cannot be tied back to you, your Account, your web browser or your TeuxDeux application.

### How and To Whom Is My Information Shared?

TeuxDeux is designed to help you share information with others. As a result, much of the information generated through TeuxDeux is shared publicly or with third parties.

#### Public TeuxDeux Activity Information:

Some of your activity on and through TeuxDeux is public by default. This includes, but is not limited to, content you have posted publicly on TeuxDeux.

Registered users may have some of this information associated with their Accounts. Unregistered users will not have this association, but information concerning their use of TeuxDeux (such as what pages they have visited) may be tracked anonymously through the use of cookies and stored by us.

Please also remember that if you choose to provide Personal Information using certain public features of TeuxDeux, then that information is governed by the privacy settings of those particular features and may be publicly available. Individuals reading such information may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge, and search engines may index that information. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including any specific information you may deem private in content that you create or information that you submit through TeuxDeux.

#### IP Address Information:

While we collect and store IP address information, that information is not made public. We do at times, however, share this information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business.

#### Information You Elect to Share:

You may access Third Party Services through TeuxDeux, for example by clicking on links to those Third Party Services from TeuxDeux. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these Third Party Services, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on or through TeuxDeux.

#### Aggregate Information:

We share Aggregate Information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners can understand how and how often people use TeuxDeux and their services or websites, which facilitates improving both their services and how we interface with them. In addition, these third parties may share with us non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-Personal Information about you that they have independently developed or acquired.

#### Email Communications:

As part of TeuxDeux, you may occasionally receive from us email and other communication relating to your Account. These emails will only be sent for purposes important to TeuxDeux, such as Account information.

#### User Profile Information:

User profile information including your username, avatars or images you elect to upload and other information you enter may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within TeuxDeux. We will not directly reveal users' email addresses to other users.

#### Information Shared with Our Agents:

We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our control (our "Agents"). We may need to share Personal Information with our Agents in order to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information with our Agents.

#### Information Disclosed Pursuant to Business Transfers:

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets associated with TeuxDeux, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

#### Information Disclosed for the Protection of Us and Others:

We also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as it reasonably believes is necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce these Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv) respond to user support requests, or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam prevention.

#### Information We Share With Your Consent:

Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

### Is Information About Me Secure?

Your Account information (including your Facebook and Twitter logins) is protected for your privacy and security. We endeavor to protect Account information to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any Account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

We otherwise store all of our information, including your IP address information, using industry-standard security techniques. We do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information about you we store, Personal Information or otherwise.

### What Information of Mine Can I Access?

You can access information associated with your Account through the TeuxDeux application. You can adjust third party services connected in your Account settings.

### How Can I Delete My Account?

Should you ever decide to delete your Account, you may do so by selecting the delete option in the settings of the Services. If you terminate and delete your Account, any association between your Account and information stored by you in connection with TeuxDeux will no longer be accessible to you. After you terminate your Account, all of your Account data, including User Content, will be removed from the Site, but such data may be retained by us indefinitely.

### What Choices Do I Have Regarding My Information?

As stated previously, you can opt not to disclose certain information to us, even though it may be needed to take advantage of some TeuxDeux features. You can delete your Account or adjust your Account's privacy settings. Please note that we will need to verify that you have the authority to delete the Account, and activity generated prior to deletion may remain stored by us.

### What Happens When There Are Changes to this Privacy Policy?

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on or within TeuxDeux or by sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses TeuxDeux after such changes have been first posted.

### What If I Have Questions or Concerns?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using TeuxDeux, please send us a detailed message to: [feedback@teuxdeux.com](mailto:feedback@teuxdeux.com). We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

_Effective Date: February 7th, 2013_
